{
    "quizzes": [
        {
            "title": "week9",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "index": 1,
                    "question": "Costs that have already been committed and cannot be recovered are",
                    "options": ["Fixed costs", "Variable costs", "Marginal costs", "Sunk costs"],
                    "correct": "Sunk costs"
                },
                {
                    "index": 2,
                    "question": "Total revenue minus total cost, including both explicit and implicit costs is a definition of",
                    "options": ["Economic profit", "Accounting profit", "Profit", "Loss"],
                    "correct": "Economic profit"
                },
                {
                    "index": 3,
                    "question": "The increase in total cost that arises from an extra unit of production are",
                    "options": ["Fixed costs", "Variable costs", "Marginal costs", "Sunk costs"],
                    "correct": "Marginal costs"
                },
                {
                    "index": 4,
                    "question": "A monopolist firm’s profit is given by",
                    "options": ["(Price - ATC) × Q", "(Price - Q) × ATC", "(ATC - Q) × Price", "Price × Q - ATC"],
                    "correct": "(Price - ATC) × Q"
                },
                {
                    "index": 5,
                    "question": "Which of the following is true for a competitive firm?",
                    "options": ["P > MR", "P > MC", "MR > MC", "MR = MC"],
                    "correct": "MR = MC"
                },
                {
                    "index": 6,
                    "question": "The amount a firm receives for the sale of its output is a definition of",
                    "options": ["Total revenue", "Total cost", "Profit", "Loss"],
                    "correct": "Total revenue"
                },
                {
                    "index": 7,
                    "question": "When the cost of production for a single firm is much lesser than the cost of production for competitive firms, we have a / an",
                    "options": ["natural monopoly", "artificial monopoly", "oligopoly", "duopoly"],
                    "correct": "natural monopoly"
                },
                {
                    "index": 8,
                    "question": "Costs that do not vary with the quantity of output produced are",
                    "options": ["fixed costs", "variable costs", "marginal costs", "sunk costs"],
                    "correct": "fixed costs"
                },
                {
                    "index": 9,
                    "question": "Costs that vary with the quantity of output produced are",
                    "options": ["fixed costs", "variable costs", "marginal costs", "sunk costs"],
                    "correct": "variable costs"
                },
                {
                    "index": 10,
                    "question": "The increase in output that arises from an additional unit of input is",
                    "options": ["marginal product", "marginal profit", "marginal loss", "marginal cost"],
                    "correct": "marginal product"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}